<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Zenatic</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Data Zenatic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Investment Portfolio Analytics &amp; Due-diligence</title>
      <link>/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description> Cashflow data input and analysis with Qlik dashboard integrations Custom designed summary report contain all analytics in Excel format Performance metrics calculations in multiple currencies Attributions and strategy based asset allocation metrics Performance benchmarked against several industry benchmarks with PME+ calculations Detailed look through data vs. summary data available at multiple levels. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Approval Integration Workflow</title>
      <link>/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description> Assist in investment decision making process and workflow Provides summaries of commitments at department, portfolio and strategy levels Tracks ongoing commitments decisions, cumulative total net commitments, unfunded &amp;amp; funded commitments, combined with investment proposals at multiple investment portfolio levels Provides look through data of total net commitments impact at transactions level Alerts when approval amount is near or breached </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portflio Analytic Matrices</title>
      <link>/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description> Provides dynamic view of the portfolio in multiple aggregation levels Standard and customized portfolio performance metrics with fully adjustable date range and periods since inception. Data extractable to excel or csv format for further analysis </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: datazenatic@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
